A Guide to the Richmond YWCA Archives 1893-1980
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series I--Executive Director (1947-1977)
  - Summer Youth Program 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15:3)
  - United Givers Fund 1962-1966 (Box-folder 15:4)
  - United Givers Fund 1967 (Box-folder 15:5)
  - United Givers Fund 1968 (Box-folder 15:6)
  - United Givers Fund 1969 (Box-folder 15:7)
  - United Givers Fund 1970 (Box-folder 15:8)
  - United Givers Fund 1971 (Box-folder 15:9)
  - United Givers Fund 1972-1973 (Box-folder 15:10)
  - United Givers Fund 1975-1977 (Box-folder 15:11)
  - YMCA/YWCA Joint Campaign 1947-1957 (Box-folder 15:12-13)
  - YMCA/YWCA Joint Campaign 1947-1957 (Box-folder 16:1)
  - YMCA/YWCA Relationships 1962-1970 (Box-folder 16:2)
  - YWCA Component-Richmond Community Action Program 1966-1969 (Box-folder 16:3)
  - Y-teen Program, Richmond Area Communtiy Council 1972 (Box-folder 16:4)
  - War Work Activities (World War I) (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Womens Press-National Magazine of YWCA 1931-1934 (Box-folder 16:6)
  - World Fellowship, National Quota 1944-1949 (Box-folder 16:7)
  - World Fellowship, National Quota 1950-1959 (Box-folder 16:8)
- Series II: Board of Directors
  - Attorney 1971-1972 (Box-folder 16:9)
  - Attorney-E.N. Tompkins 1960-1962 (Box-folder 16:10)
  - Board of Directors 1904-1909 (Box-folder 16:11)
  - Board of Directors 1918 (Box-folder 16:12)
  - Board of Directors 1919 (Box-folder 16:13)
  - Board of Directors 1920 (Box-folder 16:14)
  - Board of Directors 1921 (Box-folder 16:15)
  - Board of Directors 1922 (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Board of Directors 1923 (Box-folders 17:2)
  - Board of Directors 1924 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Board of Directors 1926 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Board of Directors 1927 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Board of Directors 1928 (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Board of Directors 1932 (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Board of Directors 1933 (Box-folder 17:8)
  - Board of Directors 1934 (Box-folder 17:9)
  - Board of Directors 1935 (Box-folder 17:10)
  - Board of Directors 1936 (Box-folder 17:11)
  - Board of Directors 1937 (Box-folder 17:12)
  - Board of Directors 1938 (Box-folder 17:13)
  - Board of Directors 1939 (Box-folder 17:14)
  - Board of Directors 1940 (Box-folder 17:15)
  - Board of Directors 1941 (Box-folder 17:16)
  - Board of Directors 1942 (Box-folder 17:17)
  - Board of Directors 1943 (Box-folder 17:18)
  - Board of Directors 1944 (Box-folder 17:19)
  - Board of Directors 1945 (Box-folder 17:20)
  - Board of Directors 1946 (Box-folder 17:21)
  - Board of Directors 1947 (Box-folder 17:22)
  - Board of Directors 1948 (Box-folder 17:23)
  - Board of Directors 1949 (Box-folder 17:24)
  - Board of Directors 1950 (Box-folder 17:25)
  - Board of Directors 1951 (Box-folder 17:26)
  - Board of Directors 1952 (Box-folder 17:27)
  - Board of Directors 1953 (Box-folder 17:28)
  - Board of Directors 1954 (Box-folder 17:29)
  - Board of Directors 1955 (Box-folder 17:30)
  - Board of Directors 1956 (Box-folder 17:31)
  - Board of Directors 1957 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Board of Directors 1958 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Board of Directors 1959 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Board of Directors 1960 (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Board of Directors 1961 (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Board of Directors 1962 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Board of Directors 1963 (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Board of Directors 1964 (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Board of Directors 1965 (Box-folder 18:9)
  - Board of Directors 1967 (Box-folder 18:10)
  - Board of Directors 1968 (Box-folder 18:11)
  - Board of Directors 1969 (Box-folder 18:12)
  - Board of Directors 1970 (Box-folder 18:13)
  - Board of Directors 1971 (Box-folder 18:14)
  - Board of Directors 1972 (Box-folder 18:15)
  - Board of Directors 1974 (Box-folder 18:16)
  - Board of Directors 1975 (Box-folder 18:17)
  - Board of Directors 1976 (Box-folder 18:18)
  - Board of Directors 1977 (Box-folder 18:19)
  - Board of Directors 1978 (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Ad hoc Fee Structure Committee 1950 (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Advisory Committee, Capital Fund Campaign 1950-1956 (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Advisory Committee, YWCA Investments with State Planters Branch 1951 (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Attendance record 1891-1908 (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Attendance records 1908-1911, 1925-1932, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Constitution, By-laws, and Job description 1969-1973 (Box-folder 19:7)
  - Jubilee (includes a history of the branch) 1916 (Box-folder 19:8)
  - Law suit 1950 (Box-folder 19:9)
  - Lumsden Fund (Box-folder 19:10-12)
  - New Board Member Kit 1976 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Presidents Correspondence-Mrs. Walker C. Cottral Jr. 1963 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Presidents Correspondence-Mrs. Garland E. Benton 1972 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Presidents Correspondence with Community Chest 1957-1960 (Box-folder 20:4)
  - President: National YWCA Centennial 1954-1956 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Secretaries Memorandum Book 1890-1907 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Scott Memorial 1948-1949 (Box-folder 20:7-8)
  - Scott Memorial Fund 1953-1956 (Box-folder 20:9)
  - Scott Memorial-Scott Speeches 1937-1948 (Box-folder 20:10)
  - Survey, Analysis and Plan of Fund Raising-John Price Jones 1960 (Box-folder 20:11)
  - Study of Capital Requirements Richmond YWCA and Floyd Hunter 1960 (Box-folder 20:12)
  - The Time for Action is Now! (Box-folder 21:1)
  - List of Members on Board 1969-1972 (Box-folder 21:2)
  - List of Members on Board 1975-1976 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Minutes-Annual Meeting of the First Meeting of the Bureau of Information for the Work of Woman's Organizations in Richmond 1898 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Minutes-Annual Meeting 1937 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1919 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1920 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1921 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1922 (Box-folder 21:9)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1923 (Box-folder 21:10)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1924 (Box-folder 21:11)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1925 (Box-folder 21:12)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1926 (Box-folder 21:13)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1927 (Box-folder 21:14)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1928 (Box-folder 21:15)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1930 (Box-folder 21:16)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1931 (Box-folder 21:17)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1932 (Box-folder 21:18)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1933 (Box-folder 21:19)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1934 (Box-folder 21:20)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1935 (Box-folder 21:21)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1936 (Box-folder 21:22)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1937 (Box-folder 21:23)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1938 (Box-folder 21:24)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1940 (Box-folder 21:25)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1941-1945 (Box-folder 21:26)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1946-1947 (Box-folder 21:27)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1948 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1950 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1951 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1952 (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1953 (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1954 (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1955 (Box-folder 22:7)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1956 (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1957 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1958 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1959 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1961 (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1962 (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1965 (Box-folder 23:7)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1966 (Box-folder 23:8)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1967 (Box-folder 23:9)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1968-1969 (Box-folder 23:10)
  - Minutes, Board of Directors 1970-1971 (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Nominating Committee 1936 (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Nominating Committee 1938 (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Nominating Committee 1939 (Box-folder 24:4)
  - Nominating Committee 1940 (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Nominating Committee 1941 (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Nominating Committee 1942 (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Nominating Committee 1943 (Box-folder 24:8)
  - Nominating Committee 1944 (Box-folder 24:9)
  - Nominating Committee 1945 (Box-folder 24:10)
  - Nominating Committee 1946 (Box-folder 24:11)
  - Nominating Committee 1947 (Box-folder 24:12)
  - Nominating Committee 1948 (Box-folder 24:13)
  - Nominating Committee 1949 (Box-folder 24:14)
  - Nominating Committee 1950 (Box-folder 24:15)
  - Nominating Committee 1951 (Box-folder 24:16)
  - Nominating Committee 1952 (Box-folder 24:17)
  - Nominating Committee 1953 (Box-folder 24:18)
  - Nominating Committee 1954 (Box-folder 24:19)
  - Nominating Committee 1955 (Box-folder 24:20)
  - Nominating Committee 1956 (Box-folder 24:21)
  - Nominating Committee 1957 (Box-folder 24:22)
  - Nominating Committee 1958 (Box-folder 24:23)
  - Nominating Committee 1959 (Box-folder 24:24)
  - Nominating Committee 1960 (Box-folder 24:25)
  - Nominating Committee 1961 (Box-folder 24:26)
  - Nominating Committee 1962 (Box-folder 24:27)
  - Nominating Committee 1963 (Box-folder 24:28)
  - Nominating Committee 1964 (Box-folder 24:29)
  - Nominating Committee 1965 (Box-folder 24:30)
  - Nominating Committee 1966 (Box-folder 24:31)
  - Nominating Committee 1967 (Box-folder 24:32)
  - Nominating Committee 1968 (Box-folder 24:33)
  - Nominating Committee 1969 (Box-folder 24:34)
  - Nominating Committee 1970 (Box-folder 24:35)
  - Nominating Committee 1971 (Box-folder 24:36)
  - Nominating Committee 1973 (Box-folder 24:37)
  - Nominating Committee 1976 (Box-folder 24:38)
  - Nominating Committee 1977 (Box-folder 24:39)
  - Role of the Board of Directors 1948 (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Annual Reports 1893 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Annual Reports 1894 (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Annual Reports 1895 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Annual Reports 1896 (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Annual Reports 1897-1898 (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Annual Reports 1899 (Box-folder 25:7)
  - Annual Reports 1900 (Box-folder 25:8)
  - Annual Reports 1901 (Box-folder 25:9)
  - Annual Reports 1903 (Box-folder 25:10)
  - Annual Reports 1904 (Box-folder 25:11)
  - Annual Reports 1909 (Box-folder 25:12)
  - Annual Reports 1910 (Box-folder 25:13)
  - Annual Reports 1911 (Box-folder 25:14)
  - Annual Reports 1912 (Box-folder 25:15)
  - Annual Reports 1913 (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Annual Reports 1914 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Annual Reports 1915 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Annual Reports 1920 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - Annual Reports 1921 (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Annual Reports 1922 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Annual Reports 1923 (Box-folder 26:7)
  - Annual Reports 1924 (Box-folder 26:8)
  - Annual Reports 1925 (Box-folder 26:9)
  - Annual Reports 1926 (Box-folder 26:10)
  - Annual Reports 1927 (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Annual Reports 1928 (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Annual Reports 1929 (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Annual Reports 1930 (Box-folder 27:4)
  - Annual Reports 1931 (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Annual Reports 1932 (Box-folder 27:6)
  - Annual Reports 1933 (Box-folder 27:7)
  - Annual Reports 1934 (Box-folder 27:8)
  - Annual Reports 1935 (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Annual Reports 1936 (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Annual Reports 1937 (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Annual Reports 1938 (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Annual Reports 1939 (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Annual Reports 1940 (Box-folder 28:6)
  - Annual Reports 1941 (Box-folder 28:7)
  - Annual Reports 1942 (Box-folder 28:8)
  - Annual Reports 1943 (Box-folder 29:1)
  - Annual Reports 1945 (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Annual Reports 1946 (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Annual Reports 1947 (Box-folder 29:4)
  - Annual Reports 1948 (Box-folder 29:5)
  - Annual Reports 1949 (Box-folder 29:6)
  - Annual Reports 1950 (Box-folder 29:7)
  - Annual Reports 1951 (Box-folder 29:8)
  - Annual Reports 1952 (Box-folder 29:9)
  - Annual Reports 1953 (Box-folder 29:10)
  - Annual Reports 1954 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Annual Reports 1955 (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Annual Reports 1956 (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Annual Reports 1957 (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Annual Reports 1958 (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Annual Reports 1959 (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Annual Reports 1969 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Annual Reports 1970 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Annual Reports 1971 (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Annual Reports 1974 (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Annual Reports 1976 (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Annual Reports 1977 (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Departmental Reports 1960 (Box-folder 31:7)
  - Departmental Reports 1961 (Box-folder 31:8)
  - Departmental Reports 1962 (Box-folder 31:9)
  - Departmental Reports 1963 (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Departmental Reports 1964 (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Departmental Reports 1965 (Box-folder 32:3)
  - Departmental Reports 1966 (Box-folder 32:4)
  - Departmental Reports 1967 (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Departmental Reports 1968 (Box-folder 32:6)
  - Annual Reports: Index Committee 1908-1911 (Box-folder 32:7)
  - Annual Reports: Index Committee 1908-1911 (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Annual Reports: Index Committee 1913 (Box-folder 33:2)
  - Annual Reports: Index Committee 1914 (Box-folder 33:3)
  - Annual Reports: Index Committee 1915 (Box-folder 33:4)
  - Annual Reports: Index Committee 1916 (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Annual Reports: Index Committee 1917 (Box-folder 33:6)
  - Annual Reports: Index Committee 1918 (Box-folder 33:7)
  - Annual Reports: Searchlight 1911 (Box-folder 33:8)
  - Annual Reports: Searchlight 1914 (Box-folder 33:9)
  - Annual Reports: Searchlight 1915 (Box-folder 33:10)
  - Annual Reports: Searchlight 1916 (Box-folder 33:11)
  - Annual Reports: Searchlight 1917 (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Annual Reports: Searchlight 1918 (Box-folder 34:2)
- Series III: Constitutions, History, Documents
  - Amendments-Virginia Child Labor Law 1947-1948 (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Anniversaries 1892, 1915, 1939, 1948, 1962 (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Annual Report of YWCA of Quebec 1898 (Box-folder 34:5)
  - Annual Report from National Board 1960-1961 (Box-folder 34:6)
  - Annual Report from National YWCA 1959-1960 (Box-folder 34:7)
  - Biennial Conference of International YWCA-Memphis 1899 (Box-folder 34:8)
  - Biennial Conference of International YWCA-Montreal 1897 (Box-folder 34:9)
  - Biennial Convention 1911 (Box-folder 35:1)
  - Biennial Convention 1913 (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Blue Ridge Institute for southern social work executives 1954 (Box-folder 35:3)
  - By laws 1954 (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Centennial Celebration 1955 (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Changes to Constitutions and Bylaws (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Consultants Report-Richmond United Givers Fund 1960-1963 (Box-folder 35:7)
  - Constitution and Bylaws 1925, 1929, 2936, 1939, 1947-1951, 1966, 1969, 1975 (Box-folder 35:8)
  - Gay Sombrero Constitution 1951 (Box-folder 35:8)
  - Helpful Handbook from YWCA (national) 1893, 1899, 1908 (Box-folder 35:9)
  - History, beginning of YWCA of Greater Richmond 1930s-1960s (Box-folder 35:10)
  - History-Year book, Richmond YWCA 1915 (Box-folder 35:11)
  - History, layouts and branches undated (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Laws regarding benefit of sales undated (Box-folder 36:2)
  - Miscellaneous programs and ephemera 1900s-1920s, undated (Box-folder 36:3)
  - National Convention 1915 (Box-folder 36:4)
  - National Convention 1936 (Box-folder 36:5)
  - National Convention 1946 (Box-folder 36:6)
  - National Convention 1949 (Box-folder 36:7)
  - National Convention 1955 (Box-folder 36:8)
  - National Convention 1976 (Box-folder 36:9)
  - National Convention and Catalogs 1969-1970 (Box-folder 36:10)
  - A National guide of participation and membership practices in YWCA 1960, 1964-1967, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 36:11)
  - National YWCA documents 1908-1916 (Box-folder 36:12)
  - Policies 1937, 1939, 1942 (Box-folder 37:1)
  - Preliminary Report of Chamberlayne Branch (includes short history on Phyllis Wheatley Branch) 1969 (Box-folder 37:2)
  - Programs 1973-1976 (Box-folder 37:3)
  - Reports of clubs and departments of branches 1920-1925, 1928 (Box-folder 37:4)
  - The Standards study from national YWCA 1936-1968 (Box-folder 37:5)
  - Statement regarding policy governing use of Lumsden Fund 1939-1940, 1946, 1951 (Box-folder 37:6)
  - Summaries and handbooks for YWCA's from national board 1948-1950, 1958, 1966 (Box-folder 37:7)
  - Training new volunteers for y-teen program 1949 (Box-folder 37:8)
  - YWCA sketches 1897 (Box-folder 37:9)
- Series IV- Budgets
  - Auditor's Report 1954 (Box-folder 38:1)
  - Auditor's Report 1965 (Box-folder 38:2)
  - Auditor's Report 1966 (Box-folder 38:3)
  - Auditor's Report 1968 (Box-folder 38:4)
  - Auditor's Report 1969 (Box-folder 38:5)
  - Budget 1922 (Box-folder 38:6)
  - Budget 1925-1932 (Box-folder 38:7)
  - Budget 1936 (Box-folder 38:8)
  - Budget 1949 (Box-folder 38:9)
  - Budget 1951 (Box-folder 38:10)
  - Budget 1952 (Box-folder 38:11)
  - Budget 1953 (Box-folder 38:12)
  - Budget 1959 (Box-folder 38:13)
  - Budget 1961 (Box-folder 38:14)
  - Budget 1962 (Box-folder 38:15)
  - Budget 1965 (Box-folder 38:16)
  - Budget 1966 (Box-folder 38:17)
  - Budget 1967 (Box-folder 38:18)
  - Budget 1968 (Box-folder 38:19)
  - Budget Information 1969 (Box-folder 38:20)
  - Budget 1970 (Box-folder 39:1)
  - Budget 1971 (Box-folder 39:2)
  - Budget 1972 (Box-folder 39:3)
  - Budget 1973 (Box-folder 39:4)
  - Budget 1974 (Box-folder 39:5)
  - Budget 1975 (Box-folder 39:6)
  - Budget 1976 (Box-folder 39:7)
  - Budget 1977 (Box-folder 39:8)
  - Budget Information 1969 (Box-folder 39:9)
  - Christian Life Committee 1970 (Box-folder 39:10)
  - Executive Director: Bon Air Community; Program Director; Development 1970-1976 (Box-folder 40:1)
  - Final Report and Evaluation-Conference on Battered Women 1977 (Box-folder 40:2)
  - Finance 1960-1970 (Box-folder 40:3)
  - Finance Committee Minutes 1941-1951 (Box-folder 40:4)
  - Finance Committee Minutes 1951-1960 (Box-folder 40:5)
  - Finance Committee Minutes 1967 (Box-folder 40:6)
  - Finance Committee, with correspondence 1944 (Box-folder 40:7)
  - Finance Committee 1946-1948 (Box-folder 40:8)
  - Financial Report 1949 (Box-folder 40:9)
  - Financial Report 1949 (Box-folder 40:10)
  - Financial Report 1950-1957 (Box-folder 40:11)
  - Financial Report Case Work 1949 (Box-folder 41:1)
  - Financial Reports 1937-1946 (Box-folder 41:2)
  - Financial Reports 1947-1948 (Box-folder 41:3)
  - Financial Reports 1951-1952 (Box-folder 41:4)
  - Financial Reports 1957-1958 (Box-folder 41:5)
  - Financial Reports 1958-1959 (Box-folder 41:6)
  - Financial Statements 1942-1946 (Box-folder 41:7)
  - Gay Sombrero Bills and Receiptsundated (Box-folder 41:8)
  - Report on Financial Statements-Young Women's Christian Association 1976 (Box-folder 41:9)
- Series V Camps
  - Applications for Camp Fernlakeundated (Box-folder 41:10)
  - Blue Triangle Cafeteriaundated (Box-folder 41:11)
  - Boarding Home, 108 West Cary 1932 (Box-folder 41:12)
  - Calhoun Community Center (Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority)1971 (Box-folder 41:13)
  - Calhoun Community Center (Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority) undated (Box-folder 41:14)
  - Camp Applications 1959 (Box-folder 42:1)
  - Camp Fernlakeundated (Box-folder 42:2-3)
  - Camp Fernlake 1971-1972 (Box-folder 42:4)
  - Camp Fernlake 1973-1976 (Box-folder 42:5)
  - Camp Fernlake 1975 (Box-folder 42:6)
  - Camp Fernlake 1967-1972 (Box-folder 42:7)
  - Camp Fernlake Construction undated (Box-folder 42:8)
  - Camp Fernlake 1964-1972 (Box-folder 42:9)
  - Camp Fernlake 1971 (Box-folder 43:1)
  - Camp Fernlake Lease 1976 (Box-folder 43:2)
  - Camp Fernlake Endowment Fund 1967-1968 (Box-folder 43:3)
  - Camp Fernlake Tax and Lease 1978 (Box-folder 43:4)
  - Camp Fernlake Woodward Property Purchase 1971-1972 (Box-folder 43:5)
  - Camp Fernlake Harrison Associates Preliminary Report 1973-1974 (Box-folder 43:6)
  - Camp Fernlake Newspaper Clippings undated (Box-folder 43:7)
  - Camp Fernlake Policiesundated (Box-folder 43:8)
  - Camp Gloucester 1959 (Box-folder 43:9)
  - Camping Applications 1954 (Box-folder 43:10)
  - Camping Committee 1955 (Box-folder 43:11)
  - Camping Information 1956-1958 (Box-folder 43:12)
  - Camping Resources 1954 (Box-folder 43:13)
  - Camp Letter 1959 (Box-folder 43:14)
  - Camp Mailing List 1957 (Box-folder 43:15)
  - Camp Matoaka undated (Box-folder 43:16)
  - Charm Camp Referrals-Industrial 1939 (Box-folder 43:17)
  - Day Camp Application Forms 1954-1955 (Box-folder 43:18)
  - Day Camp Scholarships 1948 (Box-folder 43:19)
  - Day Camp Schlorarships 1954 (Box-folder 43:20)
  - Day Camp-St. Catherine's-Lumsden Requests 1946 (Box-folder 43:21)
  - Directions to Camp Fernlake undated (Box-folder 43:22)
  - Dormitory and Restaurant Services undated (Box-folder 44:1)
  - Eaves Lake undated (Box-folder 44:2)
  - Food Service 1947-1956 (Box-folder 44:3)
  - Girl Scout Day Camp undated (Box-folder 44:4)
  - High School Girls Day Camp at Westhampton undated (Box-folder 44:5)
  - Hodge Lawn 1932-1936 (Box-folder 44:6)
  - Kaperette Kamp 1956 (Box-folder 44:7)
  - Kaperette Kamp 1958 (Box-folder 44:8)
  - Kaperette Kamp 1970 (Box-folder 44:9)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Camp 1954 (Box-fodler 44:10)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Camp 1957 (Box-folder 44:11)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Day Camp 1958 (Box-folder 44:12)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Day Camp Scholarships 1946 (Box-folder 44:13)
  - Phyllis Wheatley Day Camp and Cooperative Girl Scout 1953 (Box-folder 44:14)
  - Purpose and Goals of Fernlake undated (Box-folder 44:15)
  - St. Catherine's Day Camp 1958 (Box-folder 44:16)
  - St. Catherine's Day Camp 1959 (Box-folder 44:17)
  - Swift Creek Camp, Purchase Accounts of Swift Creek Camp by A. Noble1937 (Box-folder 44:18)
  - Walford Residence, includes photographsundated (Box-folder 44:19)
  - Walford Residence, Reports, Correspondence and Accounts 1918-1930 (Box-folder 44:20)
  - Walford Residence, Reports, Correspondence and Accounts 1918-1921 (Box-folder 44:21)
  - Walford Residence, Cash Outward 1920-1923 (Box-folder 44:22)
  - Walford Residence Finance and Property 1917-1945 (Box-folder 44:23)
  - Walford Residence Inventories 1945-1947 (Box-folder 44:24)
  - Wilson Inn 1975-1976 (Box-folder 44:25)
  - Younger Girls Day Camp 1947 (Box-folder 44:26)
  - YWCA Day Camp 1956 (Box-folder 44:27)
  - YWCA Day Camp undated (Box-folder 44:28)
  - YWCA Day Camp-St. Catherine's undated (Box-folder 44:29)
- Series VI- Case Studies
  - Abraham, Angelina (Box-folder 46:1)
  - Abrams, Sophie (Box-folder 46:2)
  - Adams, Margaret (Box-folder 46:3)
  - Aiken, Eula (Box-folder 46:4)
  - Alexander, Phyllis (Box-folder 46:5)
  - Allen, Antoinette (Box-folder 46:6)
  - Allen, Betty Jane (Box-folder 46:7)
  - Allen, Betty and Anne Cottrell (Box-folder 46:8)
  - Allen, Eunice (Box-folder 46:9)
  - Allen, Frances (Box-folder 46:10)
  - Allen, Lovetta Rae (Box-folder 46:11)
  - Allen, Marion (Box-folder 46:12)
  - Allen, Mrs. C.B. (Box-folder 46:13)
  - Alston, Virginia (Box-folder 46:14)
  - Anderson, Clara (Box-folder 46:15)
  - Anderson, Delia (Box-folder 46:16)
  - Anderson, Laura (Box-folder 46:17)
  - Anderson, Lois (Box-folder 46:18)
  - Andre, Charlotte (Box-folder 46:19)
  - Anreotti, Enis (Box-folder 46:20)
  - Applewhite, Violet (Box-folder 46:21)
  - Archer, Elsie (Box-folder 46:22)
  - Archer, Fannie (Box-folder 46:23)
  - Armstrong, Ann (Box-folder 46:24)
  - Armstrong, Barbara (Box-folder 46:25)
  - Arthur, Elsie Mae (Box-folder 46:26)
  - Ashworth Catherine (Box-folder 46:27)
  - Ashworth, Ruth (Box-folder 46:28)
  - Askins, Mary (Box-folder 46:29)
  - Atkins, Dorothy (Box-folder 46:30)
  - Atkins, Jean Marie (Box-folder 46:31)
  - Ayers, Gloria (Box-folder 46:32)
  - Ayers, Mrs. A.T. (Box-folder 46:33)
  - Babb, Anne (Box-folder 46:34)
  - Baber, Barbara (Box-folder 46:35)
  - Bagley, Alethia (Box-folder 46:36)
  - Bailey, Bernice (Box-folder 46:37)
  - Bailey, Mona (Box-folder 46:38)
  - Baker, Betty (Box-folder 46:39)
  - Ball Hope (Box-folder 46:40)
  - Barley, Pattie Frances (Box-folder 46:41)
  - Barnard, Eugene (Box-folder 46:42)
  - Barnes, Courtney (Box-folder 46:43)